# VENKATTARAMANAN CHENDRAYAPERUMAL

ramanan451@gmail.com / +919626287628 / 31-1, Muncheep thottam, kondalampatty, salem-10., salem, tamilnadu

#### Summary

Experienced and dedicated consultant with over 4 years of experience helping clients meet and exceed business goals. a challenging position in the SAP SD environment that will offer the opportunity for both professional and personal growth as well as utilize my abilities and experience.

# **Experience**

# **PPSM Senior Analyst**

General electric - Support - Accenture India Private Ltd • Bangalore, Karnataka 06/2022 - 11/2022

- · Preparing reports and delivering presentations about their recommended
- · SAP implementations or modifications.
- Understands processes and reporting requirements and user interfaces.
- impacted by the ERP system. Identifies modifications and recommends and applies changes as appropriate.
- In the Final Preparation involved in Unit Testing, Integration Testing and Final UAT using real time data in Pre-Production.
- Configuration of pricing procedure and maintaining condition records as perclient's business requirement.
- Working in P2&P3 team and handling low and medium priority tickets.
- · Attending weekly meeting and analyzing pending issues

#### Sr. SAP SD Consultant

WBN – Divimaxim Technologies Private Ltd • Hyderabad, Telangana 08/2021 - 06/2022

- Works with business users to configure the module to translate business requirements into functional design specifications.
- Problem Analyzing and Handling Tickets.
- Configuring the system to meet the requirements of the client.
- Create documentation like functional specs., functional design, back-out plans, testing results., root cause analysis document
- Maintained and updated the tickets status for tracking the tickets.
- Attending weekly meeting and analyzing pending issues.
- Handled issues raised by user according to their criticality level defined in SLA.
- Providing Production Support, Solving & Analyzing the issue to provide the solutions to the user generated error and incident.

#### **Associate Consultant**

Roger & Roger – Divimaxim Technologies Private Ltd • Hyderabad, Telangana 06/2019 - 08/2021

- Configured customer specific requirements.
- Configured document types for sales, delivery and billing.
- Configured different pricing procedures.
- Configured Third Party process, consignment process, and stock transfer process.
- Configured Availability check and Transfer of requirements.
- · Configured batch determination.
- Configured Output determination.

## **Associate Consultant**

Selena Group, CA - Divimaxim Technologies Private Ltd • Hyderabad, Telangana 05/2018 - 06/2019

- Responsible for resolving the incidents within the scope of SLA.
- Active participation in team meetings addressing methods for handling tickets efficiently.
- Reporting the deviations in resolving the issue and taking corrective actions in order to satisfy the customer.
- Communicating the status of issues and impacts with team members and Client.
- · Learned various business topics.
- · Documented the solution once the solution is completed.
- · Daily Monitoring and updating Support issues.
- Providing KT to new team members.

## **Skills**

SAP S/4HANA, SAP ECC

## **Education**

# B.E (Mechanical engineer)

Gnanamani college of technology • salem, tamilnadu 05/2018 GPA: 68%

## **HSC**

Gugai.Hr.Sec.School • Salem, Tamil Nadu 05/2014

Percentage: 85%

## **SSLC**

Gugai.Hr.Sec.School • salem, tamilnadu 05/2010

Percentage: 91.4%

#### Languages

Hindi, tamil, kannada, English